Are ya ready, kids?
孩子们，你们准备好了吗？
I can't  hear  you.
我听不到你说话。
Kids:
Aye, aye, Captain.
孩子们：
是的，是的，船长。
♪ Ohh... ♪
♪ 哦...♪
♪ Who lives in a pineapple
under the sea? ♪
♪ 谁住在菠萝里
在海底？ ♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ Absorbent and yellow
and porous is he ♪
队长：♪ 吸水性的，黄色的
他是多孔的 ♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ If nautical nonsense
be somethin' you wish ♪
船长：♪ 如果是航海方面的废话
成为你所希望的那样 ♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ Then drop on the deck
and flop like a fish ♪
船长：♪ 然后降落在甲板上
然后像鱼一样扑通扑通♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ Ready? ♪
队长：♪ 准备好了吗？ ♪
All: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
全部： ♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ SpongeBob
SquarePants ♪
队长：♪ 海绵宝宝
方裤♪
Narrator:  Shady Shoals,
mild-mannered rest home
旁白：谢迪浅滩，
温和的疗养院
and secret headquarters
of Mermaid Man
和秘密总部
人鱼男的
master of maritime justice
and defender of Bikini Bottom.
海事司法硕士
和比基尼底部的防守者。
Semi-retired.
半退休状态。
And his faithful ward
Barnacle Boy.
还有他忠实的监护人
藤壶男孩。
Who?
WHO？
世界卫生组织？
Today we find this
duo of dynamism
今天我们发现这个
活力二重奏
engaged in their favorite
pastime: watching TV.
从事自己喜欢的事
消遣：看电视。
But wait, what's this?
但是等等，这是什么？
Why, it's Mermaid Man
and Barnacle Boy's biggest fans
为什么，这是美人鱼男
和藤壶男孩的最大粉丝
SpongeBob SquarePants
and Patrick Star.
海绵宝宝
和帕特里克星。
Don't they look peaceful?
他们看起来不是很平静吗？
Yeah.
是的。
Wake up!
醒醒吧！
I'll deal with
these super-villains
我会处理
这些超级恶棍
with my trusty Mermarang!
和我值得信赖的美宝鱼一起！
Hey, those aren't
super-villains.
嘿，那些不是
超级恶棍。
Hi, Mermaid- Ow.
嗨，美人鱼——噢。
I can't believe Mermaid Man
hit me with his Mermarang.
我不敢相信美人鱼男
用他的人鱼镖攻击我。
It's so awesome.
太棒了。
Wow.
哇。
Can you beat me up next?
接下来你能打败我吗？
Keep on your guard,
Barnacle Boy.
保持警惕，
藤壶男孩。
They're getting ready
for another attack.
他们正在准备
进行另一次攻击。
Those aren't super-villains.
那些不是超级恶棍。
It's just that kid,
uh, SpongeBob,
and his goofy friend.
只是那个孩子，
呃，海绵宝宝，
和他的傻朋友。
Hey, kid, can you give us
our Mermarang back?
嘿，孩子，你能给我们吗？
我们的人鱼鱼回来了？
We only got the one.
我们只得到了一个。
Hey, sure thing.
嘿，当然可以。
Oh, don't throw-
哦，别扔——
Hey, it came back.
嘿嘿，它回来了。
Yeah,  ,
it does that.
是的，，
它就是这样做的。
I'll try again.
我会再试一次。
No-
不-
Look, I'll just
come and get-
你看，我就
来吧-
What is wrong with you?
你怎么了？
Nice shot.
好球。
Wow, that Mermarang
really likes you.
哇，那个美宝鱼
真的很喜欢你。
I know.
我知道。
Now just hand me
the Mermarang, son-
现在只要递给我
人鱼鱼，儿子——
I've got it!
我明白了！
Runaway Mermarang!
逃跑的人鱼鱼！
Ow.
噢。
SpongeBob: Hi.
海绵宝宝：嗨。
How you feeling?
你感觉怎么样？
Would you get off of me?
你愿意从我身上下来吗？
Ok.
好的。
What are you two
doing here, anyway?
你们两个是什么
无论如何，在这里做什么？
Oh, I almost forgot.
哦，我差点忘了。
I brought you flowers.
我给你带来了花。
Since you two
are feeling so poorly.
自从你们两个
感觉很糟糕。
Patrick: You never
brought  me  flowers.
帕特里克：你从来没有
给我带来了花。
Patrick, go home
and check your mailbox.
帕特里克，回家吧
并检查您的邮箱。
Really?
真的吗？
The Merma-Phone.
Merma 电话。
Mermaid Man here.
人鱼男在这里
Ah, Commissioner,
what can I do for you?
啊，专员，
我能为你做什么？
You can count on
Mermaid Man, commissioner.
您可以信赖
人鱼男，专员。
It's for you.
这是给你的。
Barnacle Boy here.
藤壶男孩在这里。
Yes, but...
是的，但是……
Yes, yes, Commissioner,
but, uh...
是的，是的，专员，
但是，呃...
The police commissioner
needs us to be
警察局长
需要我们成为
celebrity contestants
at the Bikini Bottom
shuffleboarding competition.
名人参赛者
在比基尼底部
沙狐球比赛。
But there's no way we can do it
in this condition.
但我们没有办法做到这一点
在这种情况下。
What kind of
quitter talk is that?
什么样的
放弃者的谈话是这样的吗？
We're superheroes.
我们是超级英雄。
We're going to that
shuffleboarding competition
我们要去那个
沙狐球比赛
or my name isn't...
或者我的名字不是...
Ow!
噢！
You're right, Barnacle Boy.
你是对的，藤壶男孩。
If only there were someone
to take our place.
如果有人
取代我们的位置。
Patrick and I could do it,
Mermaid Man!
帕特里克和我可以做到，
人鱼男！
What?
什么？
Why should we
trust you two?
我们为什么要
相信你们两个吗？
Because we're
card-carrying members
因为我们是
持卡会员
of the Mermaid Man
and Barnacle Boy fan club.
人鱼男的
和藤壶男孩粉丝俱乐部。
So?
所以？
Mermaid Man and Barnacle Boy
impersonators.
美人鱼人和藤壶男孩
模仿者。
Certified.
已认证。
You can't argue
with certification.
你不能争论
有认证。
Oh, all right.
哦，好吧。
I suppose they can't do
too much damage.
我想他们做不到
伤害太大。
It's just shuffleboard-
这只是沙狐球——
: We're
gonna be heroes.
: 我们是
会成为英雄。
We're gonna be heroes.
我们会成为英雄。
Would you
cut it out?
你愿意吗
剪掉它吗？
Would you cut it out?
你会把它剪掉吗？
Heroes, heroes, he-roes?
英雄，英雄，男英雄？
Now listen up.
现在听着。
Here, take these rings.
来，拿走这些戒指。
Oh...
哦...
And when you touch 'em together
当你触摸它们的时候
you'll be instantly transformed
into our duplicates.
你会立刻变身
进入我们的副本。
Mermaid Man
and Barnacle Boy, unite!
人鱼男
和藤壶男孩，团结起来！
We're ready.
我们准备好了。
Man-bob.
曼鲍勃。
And Pat-boy.
还有帕特男孩。
Reporting for duty.
报到值班。
When you're through with
shuffleboarding
当你完成时
沙狐球
you're to bring those costumes
right back here.
你要带上那些服装
就回到这里。
And  don't  do anything else.
并且不要做任何其他事情。
Don't go home first,
don't show your friends
先别回家
不要给你的朋友看
just come right back here,
you got it?
刚回到这里，
你明白了吗？
Got it.
知道了。
This'll never work.
这永远行不通。
What will never work?
什么永远行不通？
Shuffleboarding,
shuffleboarding,
shuffleboarding!
沙狐球、
沙狐球，
沙狐球！
Shuffleboarding is exciting,
huh, Patrick?
沙狐球很刺激，
嗯，帕特里克？
Well, duh.
嗯，呃。
What's your favorite thing
about shuffleboarding?
你最喜欢什么
关于沙狐球？
Everything.
一切。
It's even fun
just to say the word.
还挺好玩的
只是为了说这个词。
: Shuffleboard.
：沙狐球。
Shuffle-el-el-el-board.
洗牌-el-el-el-board。
Ah, it is fun.
啊，很有趣。
We're gonna seriously
kick some elderly buns today.
我们要认真的
今天踢一些老人包子。
Huh, SpongeBob?
哈，海绵宝宝？
What?
什么？
Out of the way, Gramps.
让开，爷爷。
That's my trophy,
old lady.
那是我的奖杯
老太太。
Patrick?
帕特里克？
It's gonna be
an action-packed thrill ride
将会是
充满动感的惊险旅程
of geriatric proportions.
的老年人比例。
And the best part is
最好的部分是
there is  no  way we can lose
with these costumes on.
我们不可能失败
穿上这些服装。
We already won the tournament.
我们已经赢得了比赛。
Oh, yeah, I forgot.
哦，是的，我忘了。
Well, how come
I didn't get a trophy?
嗯，怎么会呢
我没拿到奖杯？
You did, it's in
your back pocket.
你做到了，它在
你的后口袋。
Oh, yeah, I forgot.
哦，是的，我忘了。
Well, let's go
do something else.
好吧，我们走吧
做点别的事。
Ok.
好的。
You're to bring those costumes
right back here.
你要带上那些服装
就回到这里。
Don't do anything else.
不要做任何其他事情。
Patrick, stop!
帕特里克，停下来！
We can't.
我们不能。
We have to
get the costumes back.
我们必须
把服装拿回来。
For Neptune's sake,
SpongeBob.
为了海王星的缘故，
海绵宝宝。
If  we're  not
gonna go around town
如果我们不是
要去城里转转
pretending to be
Mermaid Man and Barnacle Boy
假装是
美人鱼人和藤壶男孩
then who is?
那么是谁呢？
Uh, nobody?
呃，没人吗？
Exactly.
确切地。
And with no one
patrolling the town
而且没有人的情况下
镇上巡逻
who's gonna stop
those youngsters from loitering?
谁会停下来
那些闲逛的年轻人？
Their mommies?
他们的妈妈？
No, we are.
不，我们是。
Let's take 'em to the slammer.
让我们带他们去监狱吧。
Patrick!
帕特里克！
"Too harsh"?
“太严厉”？
Explain.
解释。
Mermaid man and Barnacle Boy?
美人鱼男和藤壶男孩？
What are you doing here?
你在这里做什么？
Ugh.
啊。
Wasting a Krabby Patty?
浪费蟹黄饼？
How could you?
你怎么可以？
I'm full.
我吃饱了。
Well, maybe somebody
should've thought about that
好吧，也许有人
应该考虑一下
before they ponied up for
the world's greatest patty...
在他们付钱之前
世界上最大的肉饼...
Mr. jail warden.
监狱长先生。
You're right, Pat-boy,
this town needs us.
你说得对，帕特男孩，
这个小镇需要我们。
You're chewing too loud.
你咀嚼的声音太大了。
Ow.
噢。
Your shoe's untied.
你的鞋带解开了。
You're too old.
你太老了。
SpongeBob: Ah, I think
we've done our work, Patrick.
海绵宝宝：啊，我想
我们已经完成了我们的工作，帕特里克。
Now let's return
these costumes.
现在让我们返回
这些服装。
That's the evil Man-Ray.
那是邪恶的曼雷。
What diabolical plan
could he be up to?
什么邪恶的计划
他能做到吗？
Why, hello, Ray.
为什么，你好，雷。
Mabel, I haven't seen you
since high school.
梅布尔，我没见过你
从高中开始。
Look at him, Patrick.
看看他，帕特里克。
Plotting with his evil minion.
与他邪恶的爪牙密谋。
Say, could I borrow
some of your detergent?
说，我可以借吗
你的一些洗涤剂？
Why, certainly.
为什么，当然。
Anything for the gal
I went to the prom with.
为了妹子什么都可以
我和我一起去参加舞会。
I'll be he's handing off
some secret weapon.
我会被他移交
一些秘密武器。
Time to crash this party.
是时候让这个聚会崩溃了。
You haven't aged a day, Ray.
你一天也没变老，雷。
Oh, you.
哦，你。
SpongeBob: Hello, Man-Ray.
海绵宝宝：你好，曼雷。
Who's your friend?
谁是你的朋友？
Hey, Mermaid Man
and Barnacle Boy.
嘿，人鱼男
和藤壶男孩。
I'd like you to meet Mabel.
我想让你见见梅布尔。
Any friend of Ray's
is a friend of mine.
雷的任何朋友
是我的一个朋友。
All right, Mabel,
that's enough chit-chat.
好吧，梅布尔，
闲聊就够了。
Now are you gonna come quietly
or we will have to take you
to jail by force?
现在你要悄悄地来吗
否则我们就得带你去
强行入狱？
Playing dumb, eh?
装傻吧？
You handle Man-Ray.
你对付曼雷。
I'll take care of his lackey.
我会照顾他的跟班。
Mabel?
梅布尔？
SpongeBob: Hai-yah!
海绵宝宝：哈喽！
Eat dryer sheets, Man-Ray.
吃烘干机床单，曼雷。
It's on now.
现在已经开始了
Filthy shorts attack.
肮脏的短裤袭击。
Clothes basket bombardment.
衣物篮轰炸。
Surrender... Mermaid Man?
投降……人鱼男？
Ow, that's it.
噢，就是这样。
Time for the spin cycle.
旋转周期的时间。
Not so fast, Man-Ray.
没那么快，曼雷。
Wha...?
世界卫生大会...？
You're all wet.
你都湿透了
You need to dry out.
你需要擦干。
What?
什么？
No, my head is dry clean only...
不，我的头只是干洗过的......
: But
I didn't do anything.
：但是
我什么也没做。
Just keep moving.
继续前进。
You too, missy.
你也是，小姐。
Well, our work is done here.
好了，到这里我们的工作就完成了。
Man: My legs, my legs...
男：我的腿，我的腿……
Woman: Dr. Forrest, dial one...
女：福雷斯特博士，请拨一个……
Mermaid Man: Good job, boys.
美人鱼男：干得好，孩子们。
You won the tournament
and returned the costumes.
你赢得了比赛
并归还了服装。
Thanks again, boys.
再次感谢，孩子们。
Just doing our merma-duty.
只是履行我们的人鱼职责。
And then some.
然后是一些。
"And then some,"
that's good.
“然后还有一些，”
那很好。
Good-bye, young men.
再见，年轻人。
Oh, look, we have more visitors.
哦，看，我们有更多的访客。
Woman: There they are,
oh, get 'em.
女：他们在那里，
哦，得到他们。
Looking good, Man-Ray.
看起来不错，曼雷。
Faster, you old coot.
快点，你这个老笨蛋。
They have so many fans.
他们有很多粉丝。
Thank you.
谢谢。
Ah.
啊。
Isn't it grand?
是不是很盛大呢？
What is?
什么是？
He's such a great musician.
他是一位非常伟大的音乐家。
He doesn't even have to touch
an instrument to be brilliant.
他甚至不需要碰触
一个辉煌的乐器。
All right, I've had enough.
好吧，我受够了。
Bunch of nonsense.
一堆废话。
Why, here he comes now.
哎呀，他现在来了。
It  is  him.
是他。
Huh?
啊？
Aren't you the esteemed
Squilliam Fancyson the Third
你不是尊贵的吗
斯奎利姆·奇森三世
who we all came here
to see perform tonight?
我们都来这里的人
今晚去看演出吗？
No, I am not.
不，我不是。
Nor would I ever want to be.
我也不想成为这样的人。
I am quite content being
Squidward Q. Tentacles.
我很满足
章鱼哥 Q. 触手。
Oh, dear.
哦亲爱的。
Well, that's too bad.
嗯，那太糟糕了。
Why?
为什么？
Because I'm head matron
因为我是女校长
at an esteemed
musical college in town
在受人尊敬的
镇上的音乐学院
and thought if you  were
Squilliam Fancyson
并想如果你是
斯奎利安·范西森
I would offer you
the high-Paying
我愿意为你提供
高薪者
and prestigious opportunity
和享有盛誉的机会
to come there and teach
your very own music class.
去那里教书
你自己的音乐课。
My very own music class?
我自己的音乐课？
Did you say
"Squilliam Fancyson"?
你说
“斯奎利亚姆·幻想森”？
Yes.
是的。
I'm...
我是...
Squilliam Fancyson.
斯奎利亚姆·凡西森。
But didn't you
just say a minute ago
但你没有吗
就说一分钟前
that your name was
Squidward Q. Tentacles?
你的名字是
章鱼哥问：触手？
It is- no, I mean, uh,
no, no, I didn't.
它是——不，我是说，呃，
不，不，我没有。
Well, that's a relief.
嗯，这真是一种解脱。
I mean, what kind of a moron
我的意思是，什么样的白痴
would go to their
worst enemy's music recital?
会去他们的
最坏的敌人的音乐演奏会？
A very pathetic one,
that's whom.
非常可悲的一个人，
就是那个人。
Indeed.
的确。
Oh.
哦。
Well, good evening,
Professor squilliam.
嗯，晚上好，
斯奎林教授。
Who?
WHO？
世界卫生组织？
Uh, um, uh, and
a good evening to you as well.
呃，嗯，呃，还有
也祝你晚安。
Hmm, music types.
嗯，音乐类型。
Oh, they're so strange.
哦，他们太奇怪了。
Good evening, students.
晚上好，同学们。
Now our first...
现在我们的第一个...
Good evening, Professor.
晚上好，教授。
As I was saying...
正如我所说...
Our first...
我们的第一个...
Yes.
是的。
Aren't you gonna
write your name on the board
like most professors do?
你难道不打算
把你的名字写在黑板上
像大多数教授一样？
My, my name, what for?
我的，我的名字，有什么用？
Well, you know,
it just seems like
嗯，你知道，
看起来就像
teachers usually write
their names on the board
the first day of class.
老师通常会写
他们的名字在黑板上
上课的第一天。
Why don't  you  come
write  your  name on the board?
你为什么不来
把你的名字写在黑板上？
We'll see how you like it.
我们会看看你喜欢它。
Ok.
好的。
There, now how does
that feel, "Billy"?
那里，现在怎么样
那种感觉，“比利”？
Ok, I, I guess.
好吧，我，我猜。
Good.
好的。
Now why don't you take your seat
现在你为什么不坐下来
and stop poking your nose
into other people's business?
别再戳你的鼻子了
介入别人的事？
Now if we can
go for five minutes
现在如果我们可以
走五分钟
without having
any further interruptions,
I'd would like to...
没有
任何进一步的中断，
我愿意...
Hey, look, it's Squid-
嘿，看，这是鱿鱼——
Uh, "Squilliam," everybody,
he was about to say "Squilliam."
呃，“斯奎利姆”，大家，
他正要说“Squilliam”。
Oh, uh, oh, actually, I think
he was about to say "Squid-"
哦哦哦其实我觉得
他正想说“鱿鱼——”
Didn't you two nincompoops know
难道你们两个白痴不知道吗
I had my name legally changed
to "Squilliam Fancyson"?
我已合法更改姓名
到“斯奎利亚姆·幻想森”？
And you are to refer to me
only as Professor Squilliam
你要提到我
仅作为斯奎利姆教授
from now until the end of time.
从现在到时间的尽头。
Now blink twice
so I know you understand.
现在眨眼两次
所以我知道你明白。
Ok, good.
好的，很好。
Hey, he blinked three times.
嘿嘿，他眨了三下眼睛。
Wow, only eight minutes in
哇，只有八分钟
and we've already
been given a math quiz.
我们已经
进行了数学测验。
Very advanced music class,
huh, Patrick?
非常高级的音乐课，
嗯，帕特里克？
I'll say.
我会说。
Would you two numbskulls
mind telling me
你们两个笨蛋愿意吗
介意告诉我
what you're doing in
music class, anyway?
你在做什么
音乐课，无论如何？
Sure.
当然。
Patrick's New Year's resolution
was to learn to play
an instrument.
帕特里克的新年决心
是为了学玩
一种乐器。
You told me your resolution
was to sign up for
你告诉我你的决心
是要报名
an all-natural, slimming,
toning, and increased
muscle mass program.
纯天然、瘦身、
调色，并增加
肌肉质量计划。
It was.
是的。
I traded with SpongeBob.
我和海绵宝宝交易。
And I have been really happy
with the results, see?
我真的很开心
结果，看到了吗？
Wow, those  are
impressive results.
哇，那些是
令人印象深刻的结果。
As you may not be aware
正如你可能不知道的那样
music is a...
音乐是一...
Music is a...
: Music is
a complicated series of...
: 音乐是
一系列复杂的...
is a complicated series of notes
that, when played in the...
是一系列复杂的笔记
那个，当玩在...
SpongeBob, do you mind?
海绵宝宝，你介意吗？
There are other people here
besides you, you know.
这里还有其他人
除了你，你知道。
And I don't think
they appreciate  you
depriving them of  my  wisdom.
我不认为
他们欣赏你
剥夺他们我的智慧。
I'm sorry,
"Professor Squilliam."
对不起，
“史奎利姆教授。”
Patrick here keeps
tickling my foot.
帕特里克在这里保留
挠我的脚。
No way, he's making that up.
不可能，他正在弥补。
It was him.
是他。
You expect me to believe
he was tickling himself?
你期望我相信
他在给自己挠痒痒吗？
You better tell him, SpongeBob.
你最好告诉他，海绵宝宝。
All right, it was me.
好吧，是我。
You were tickling yourself.
你在给自己挠痒痒。
Mm-hmm.
嗯嗯。
How?
如何？
All right, that's enough!
好吧，够了！
There.
那里。
Now, as I was saying
现在，正如我所说
music is a series of complex...
音乐是一系列复杂的...
SpongeBob, I told you
to stop tickling yourself.
海绵宝宝，我告诉过你了
停止给自己挠痒痒。
Actually, that time...
It really was me.
其实那个时候...
确实是我。
Now I'm going to put some notes
on the chalkboard.
现在我要写一些笔记
在黑板上。
Excuse me?
打扰一下？
Is this something
you'd like to share with
the rest of the class?
这是什么东西吗
你想与人分享
班里剩下的人呢？
Uh-uh.
呃呃。
Go on, you've already
interrupted once.
继续吧，你已经
中断一次。
You might as well tell us
what was so very important.
你不妨告诉我们
什么如此重要。
Well...
出色地...
I was just saying that
these lines you drew
我只是这么说
你画的这些线
remind me of a railroad track.
让我想起了一条铁轨。
I've never heard anything
insipid, insane
我从来没听说过什么
平淡的，疯狂的
uninteresting or irrelevant.
无趣或无关紧要。
Well, actually, there  was
a railroad convention
in town last week
嗯，实际上，有
铁路会议
上周在城里
and I bought myself this
nifty conductor's cap.
我给自己买了这个
漂亮的指挥帽。
I have never seen a more
ridiculous-looking object
我从未见过更多
看起来可笑的物体
on top of
anybody's head  anywhere.
在上面
任何人的头在任何地方。
Well, I don't know,
suits my needs.
嗯，我不知道，
适合我的需要。
What else did you buy
at this convention?
你还买了什么
在这次大会上？
Your very own locomotive?
你自己的机车？
Yes.
是的。
- What the?
- 什么？
Now where were...
现在在哪里...
We?
我们？
This is what's known as
a metronome.
这就是所谓的
节拍器。
Hey, my mom has one of those
in her garden.
嘿，我妈妈有一个
在她的花园里。
Oh, no, SpongeBob.
哦，不，海绵宝宝。
That was a garden gnome.
那是一个花园侏儒。
Anyway.
反正。
The metronome
helps us keep time.
节拍器
帮助我们保持时间。
SpongeBob And Patrick: Tick,
tick, tick, tick, tick...
海绵宝宝和帕特里克：勾选，
勾勾，勾勾，勾勾，勾勾……
Tick, tick, tick, tick....
勾勾、勾勾、勾勾、勾勾......
Do you mind?
你介意吗？
Tick, tick, tick, tick, tick...
滴答、滴答、滴答、滴答、滴答……
Is there something seriously
wrong with your heads?
有什么严重的事吗
你的头有问题吗？
My whole life has been
pointed in one direction.
我的一生都是
指向一个方向。
I see that now.
我现在明白了。
There's never been
any choice for me.
从来没有过
对我来说任何选择。
Would you two nincompoops
cut it out?
你们两个笨蛋愿意吗
剪掉它吗？
Or am I gonna...
还是我要...
Hello.
你好。
We're with the local
Bikini Bottom news channel.
我们和当地人一起
比基尼底部新闻频道。
I'm a reporter.
我是一名记者。
We're here to conduct
an interview with
我们来这里是为了进行
采访
the esteemed musical genius
Squilliam Fancyson.
受人尊敬的音乐天才
斯奎利亚姆·凡西森。
SpongeBob And Patrick: Tick,
tick, tick, tick, tick...
海绵宝宝和帕特里克：勾选，
勾勾，勾勾，勾勾，勾勾……
Tick, tick, tick, tick...
Please ignore them.
请忽略他们。
Are those students of yours?
那些学生是你的吗？
Nope, they're just morons.
不，他们只是白痴。
Come on, you two,
snap out of it.
来吧，你们两个，
摆脱它。
They appear to be
in some type of trance.
他们似乎是
处于某种恍惚状态。
A case of genuine
hypnosis like this
正品案例
像这样的催眠
makes a much hotter scoop.
做了一个更热的勺子。
Hotter scoop?
更热的勺子？
Well, it's the sort of thing
that borders on the paranormal.
嗯，就是这样的事情
这接近于超自然现象。
Our viewers just
eat that stuff up.
我们的观众只是
把那些东西吃掉。
Paranormal?
超自然现象？
The only thing paranormal
around here
唯一的超自然现象
在这附近
is how fast I'm gonna
make you two disappear.
我要多快
让你们两个消失。
Don't blame me...
别怪我...
Blame the market...
归咎于市场...
What, where am I?
什么，我在哪儿？
I felt like I was in
some sort of horrible trance.
我感觉我就像在
某种可怕的恍惚状态。
You want to know what happened?
你想知道发生了什么吗？
Ok.
好的。
You once again managed to
single-handedly annihilate
你再一次成功了
单枪匹马歼灭
what might be the one and only
chance I may ever get
什么可能是唯一的
我可能得到的机会
to sow just one tiny seed
of creative hope
只播下一颗微小的种子
充满创造性的希望
into the culturally barren
wasteland
进入文化贫瘠之地
荒地
that each and every one of us
is forced to call home.
我们每一个人
被迫打电话回家。
Actually, I've been
commuting from upstate.
其实我一直
从北部通勤。
Now I don't suppose you two
have anything to say
for yourselves.
现在我不认为你们两个
有话要说
为了你们自己。
Well, I guess if I was
to say one thing
好吧，我想如果我是
说一件事
it would have to be...
一定是……
We're sorry, Squidward.
我们很抱歉，章鱼哥。
Yeah, we're sorry,
Squidward.
是的，我们很抱歉，
章鱼哥。
No-no-no,
shh-shh-shh.
不不不，
嘘-嘘-嘘。
Hey, did those guys
just call you Squidward?
嘿，那些人是吗？
就叫你章鱼哥吧？
No-no-no-no-no,
they said Squilliam.
不不不不不，
他们说斯奎利姆。
Ugh, I knew this guy
was a phony from minute one.
呃，我认识这个人
从第一分钟起就是一个骗子。
I'm getting out of here.
我要离开这里。
Yeah, me too.
是的，我也是。
I'm gonna get my tuition back.
我要把我的学费拿回来
No, wait.
不，等等。
no!
不！
You're not going anywhere.
你哪儿也去不了。
What, what's going on here?
什么，这是怎么回事？
Sorry, Professor,
your little symphony is over.
对不起，教授，
你的小交响曲结束了。
It's true, we're on to
your little ruse.
这是真的，我们正在努力
你的小诡计。
What a hot scoop.
多么热门的一勺。
The real Squilliam,
as we all know
真正的斯奎利姆，
众所周知
has a large, bushy unibrow just
at the base of his forehead.
有一个又大又浓密的一字眉
在他额头的底部。
But...
但...
No unibrow.
没有一字眉。
Squidward Q. Tentacles,
I'm placing you under arrest
章鱼哥Q.触手，
我要逮捕你
for impersonating a genius.
因为冒充天才。
Tick, tick, tick, tick, tick...
滴答、滴答、滴答、滴答、滴答……